http://www.perthcathedral.co.uk/privacy-policy/

HomeWorshipWho We AreHistoryOur Ministry TeamCathedral LifeMusicMagazineCommunityEventsVisiting usBook our venueOnline WorshipNewsContact
Menu
HomeWorshipWho We AreHistoryOur Ministry TeamCathedral LifeMusicMagazineCommunityEventsVisiting usBook our venueOnline WorshipNewsContact
Data Protection and Privacy Policy
This page explains our approach to privacy on our website and how it affects you.
In short, the following applies to our website:
We collect anonymous usage statistics about your visit, like which of our pages you viewed.
Some third parties like Facebook and Twitter may know you visited this website, if you use their services. We can't control them but we don't believe this knowledge poses any threat to you.
If you share personally identifiable information with us we take great care to keep it safe and we'll never share it with others without your express permission.
We never share your data with third parties except to help us deliver our own services.
These are just the key points. If you need details, keep reading.
Website Compliance
We regularly review the beautifulperth.org website for GDPR compliance and make updates as appropriate. The website uses the HTTPS protocol.
Cookies
Like most websites, we use cookies. Cookies are small pieces of data that websites store in their visitors' web browsers. Other technologies, including data we store on your web browser or device, identifiers associated with your device, and other software, are used for similar purposes. In this policy, we refer to all of these technologies as "cookies". Cookies help to improve our services and give you a better experience. For example, they can show us which pages people visit most often, and which are not getting as much attention. If you wish to block cookies you can do this in your browser settings; you can learn more about cookies and how to block them here.
Emails
If you provide us with your email address we may send you emails, either in reply to specific enquiries (such as one made using a contact form) or if you have opted in to our email newsletters. You have the ability to opt out of any of this communication at any time.
We will never provide your personal information or email address to any third parties except where they are specifically employed to help deliver our own services.
Google Analytics
We measure visitors to our website using Google Analytics. This records what pages you view within our site, how you arrived at our site and some basic information about your computer, such as the web browser you use and the screen resolution. All of that information is anonymous - so we don't know who you are; just that somebody visited our site.
The information we collect from analytics helps us understand what parts of our sites are doing well, how people arrive at our site and so on. Like most websites, we use this information to make our website better.
Any data collected by Google Analytics that is associated with cookies, user identifiers or advertising identifiers is retained for a period of up to 26 months.
You can learn more about Google Analytics or opt out  if you wish.
Things you can do
You have legal control over your personal data, and so you may at any time:
get a copy of any personal data we hold about you
have any incorrect, inaccurate or incomplete data corrected
ask that personal data be erased when it's no longer needed
ask that your data is not used for marketing purposes
If you need to do so then please get in touch with us using the details below.
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or your personal data, please write to us by email to Enable JavaScript to view protected content. or by post to: St Ninian’s Cathedral, North Methven Street, Perth, PH1 5PP.
